Contact

16 oktobra 11/7 11050 Beograd +381641234297 (Mobile) nemanjasimeunovic@hotmail.r s

www.linkedin.com/in/nemanjasimeunovic-24b67652 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Talent Management
Organizational Development
HR Consulting

Nemanja Simeunovic

Administrator at Secut doo

Belgrade

Summary

Experienced Human Resources Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the human resources industry. Skilled in Talent Management, HR Consulting, Organizational Development, Management Consulting, and Business Strategy. Strong human resources professional with a Master of Business Administration (MBA) focused in international management from Faculty of International Management

Experience

Secut doo Administrator March 2021 - Present (10 months) Belgrade, Serbia

G2 FALCON 2017 d.o.o. - Belgrade HR Manager March 2018 - March 2021 (3 years 1 month) Serbia

- Complete management of human resources,
- Creation of employment contract
- Contract of work,
- Contract of the temporary part-time jobs
- Check and check-out workers electronic and physical means (CR, PIO, Health Insurance Fund),

Siom Invest d.o.o. HR Manager June 2011 - March 2018 (6 years 10 months) Beograd, Srbija

- Complete management of human resources,
- Creation of employment contract
- Contract of work,
- Contract of the temporary part-time jobs

- Check and check-out workers electronic and physical means (CR, PIO, Health Insurance Fund), performing the entire procedure for issuing health cards, sick-leave an professional injuries

NATIONAL EMPLOYMENT SERVICE

Associate for employment programs

June 2006 - August 2007 (1 year 3 months)

Pancevo, Srbija

Correspondence between employers and the unemployed

Rolex Enginnering Project Manager August 2005 - April 2006 (9 months) Belgrade

Negotiations with partners

Presence in tenders

Marketing assistance

YUTA - Associations of Serbian and Montenegrian Travel Agencies Junior Associate

January 2002 - January 2003 (1 year 1 month)

Belgrade, Serbia

- International relations (UFTAA, IATA, RDA, TURSAB, EURO<26, ESB English school of business), PR
- Updating web

Ukranian Oil company Regional HR Manager June 2000 - October 2000 (5 months) Limassol, Cyprus

Regruting candtates from EX YU contries HR selection Completing procedure for working permits

Health insurance

Bank of Cyprus Volunteer July 1999 - December 1999 (6 months) Limassol, Cyprus

- Credit and loan department
- Assistant in HR Department

Education

Faculty of the International Management
Master of Business Administration (MBA), International
management · (1996 - 2000)